deke.com 2013-04-13

# Privacy Policy | dekeOnline

**DEKEONLINE***

* wholly owned and operated by Type & Graphics Inc.,a Colorado corporation.

**dekeOnline values its members and is committed to protecting their privacy.**

**dekeOnline does not sell, rent, or lease any information supplied by its members.**

This Privacy Policy provides dekeOnline members with an overview of the measures it takes to protect personal information received through dekeOnline.

Further, this Privacy Policy applies to dekeOnline (also known as [www.deke.com](http://www.deke.com/ "www.deke.com"), but referred to herein as “dekeOnline”) and any other site owned and/or operated by or on behalf of dekeOnline, and governs data collected and its usage on these websites. By using or visiting dekeOnline, the member consents to the data practices described in this Policy.

**Collection of Members’ Personal Information and Use of Member Information**

dekeOnline may collect personally identifiable information, such as a member’s e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number.

dekeOnline may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to a member, such as a member’s Postal Code, age, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites. dekeOnline does not delete member information for current members.

dekeOnline collects and uses personal information to operate the dekeOnline website and deliver the services members request. dekeOnline will send an initial email following registration to all registered members. Periodically, dekeOnline will send to registered members:

  * service updates regarding dekeOnline
  * newsletters from dekeOnline
  * alerts to news or events on dekeOnline
  * information about contests or giveaways sponsored by dekeOnline

In addition, dekeOnline may collect online and use personally identifiable information from members: (1) in connection with contests, content submissions, and visitors' requests for information; and (2) to customize the content on our site for members’ current and future needs. dekeOnline may also use personally identifiable information to inform a member of products or services available from dekeOnline. dekeOnline may also contact members via surveys to conduct research about members’ opinions of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

dekeOnline may also use personally identifiable information to inform members of opinions or recommendations regarding third party products. Such opinions or recommendations are those of dekeOnline alone. No commercial or financial gain is received by dekeOnline, Deke McClelland or Type&Graphics, Inc. as a result of these opinions or recommendations. dekeOnline does not sell, rent, or lease its member lists to third parties. But, dekeOnline may, from time to time, contact a member on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to a member. In those cases, a member’s unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, dekeOnline may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send email to members, or provide customer support. All such third parties are prohibited from using personal information of dekeOnline members except to provide these services to dekeOnline, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information. dekeOnline keeps track of the websites and pages members visit within dekeOnline, in order to determine what dekeOnline services are the most utilized. This data is used to deliver customized content within dekeOnline to members whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. dekeOnline websites will disclose a member’s personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on dekeOnline or the site;
  * protect and defend the rights or property of dekeOnline; and,
  * act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of members of dekeOnline, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

dekeOnline collects non-personally identifiable information through the use of a software technology called "cookies," through pixel tags, and through members' voluntary submissions to dekeOnline and/or upon member requests. A cookie is a text file that is placed on a hard disk drive by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to a member’s computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to a member, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to the member.

Among other things, the non-personally identifiable information collected through cookies allows dekeOnline to know which areas are favorites, which areas need a bit of improvement, or what technologies and Internet services are being used by members so that it may continually improve the online experiences of members of dekeOnline.

Most web browsers give a member a way to refuse or disable most cookies (but not Flash cookies). If a member chooses to disable, refuse, reject or delete cookies, some of the functionality of dekeOnline may no longer be available.

**Protection and Storage of Personal Information**

dekeOnline ensures that all personally and non-personally identifiable information that it receives via the Internet is secure against unauthorized access.

This information is kept on a private, dedicated server in a manner that ensures it remains safe and secure, isolated from direct connection to the Internet. Members may request additional information about the storage of their information by contacting dekeOnline as set forth below.

**Contact Information and Changes to Privacy Policy**

The contact information for dekeOnline is on the website and remains current and updated.

Any changes to this Policy also are reflected on dekeOnline. Periodically, changes are made to this Policy, to better serve members or to reflect changes in the Internet environment. As all members are subject to this Policy, members are encouraged to periodically review the Policy to be informed as to the protection of member information on dekeOnline.
